All the magic of Disney's legendary classic continues.
Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas is a animation,
family, fantasy film directed by Andrew Knight.
Astonished to find the Beast has a deep-seated hatred for the Christmas
season, Belle endeavors to change his mind on the matter.
Belle (voice), played by Paige O'Hara.
Beast (voice), played by Robby Benson.
Lumiere (voice), played by Jerry Orbach.
Cogsworth (voice), played by David Ogden Stiers.
Angelique (voice), played by Bernadette Peters.
Forte (voice), played by Tim Curry.
Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas is a 1997 direct-to-video animated Christmas musical fantasy film produced by Walt Disney
Television Animation and Disneytoon Studios, as a sequel to Disney's 1991 animated feature film Beauty and the Beast.
The film was released by Walt Disney Home Video on November 11, 1997.
While a frame story is set after the events of the original film, the main narrative is
a flashback recounting Belle and the Beast's first Christmas together.
The film sold 7.6 million VHS tapes in 1997.
The film explores themes of fairy tale, cartoon, christmas.
The tone is thought_provoking.